Richard Scarry Papers 1997.0048
Archives & Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Libraries
- Series II: Children's Literature, undated, 1965-1993
  - Best First Book Ever, 1979
    - Black and white separation (pages 24-25), ca. 1979 (Box OS:, Folder 691)
    - Black and white separation (pages 26-27), ca. 1979 (Box OS:, Folder 692)
    - Black and white separation (pages 28-29), ca. 1979 (Box OS:, Folder 693)
    - Black and white separation (pages 30-31), ca. 1979 (Box OS:, Folder 694)
    - Black and white separation (pages 32-33), ca. 1979 (Box OS:, Folder 695)
    - Black and white separation (pages 34-35), ca. 1979 (Box OS:, Folder 696)
    - Black and white separation (pages 36-37), ca. 1979 (Box OS:, Folder 697)
    - Black and white separation (pages 38-39), ca. 1979 (Box OS:, Folder 698)
    - Black and white separation (pages 40-41), ca. 1979 (Box OS:, Folder 699)
    - Black and white separation (pages 42-43), ca. 1979 (Box OS:, Folder 700)
    - Black and white separation (pages 44-45), ca. 1979 (Box OS:, Folder 701)
  - Best Grow Chart Ever, undated
    This chart was done as a promotion for Pampers® diapers.
    - Black and white and color separations (instructions page), undated (Box OS:, Folder 896)
    - Black and white and color separations (health page 1), undated (Box OS:, Folder 897)
    - Black and white and color separations (health page 2), undated (Box OS:, Folder 898)
    - Black and white and color separations (chart to 20 inches / 50 cm), undated (Box OS:, Folder 899)
    - Black and white and color separations (chart 20-40 inches / 51-101 cm), undated (Box OS:, Folder 900)
    - Black and white and color separations (chart 40-57 inches / 102-145 cm), undated (Box OS:, Folder 901)
  - Best Little Word Book Ever, 1992
    - Black and white and color separations (cover), ca. 1992 (Box OS:, Folder 702)
    - Black and white, color, and text separations (title page), ca. 1992 (Box OS:, Folder 703)
    - Black and white, color, and text separations (pages 2-3), ca. 1992 (Box OS:, Folder 704)
    - Black and white, color, and text separations (pages 4-5), ca. 1992 (Box OS:, Folder 705)
    - Black and white, color, and text separations (pages 6-7), ca. 1992 (Box OS:, Folder 706)
    - Black and white, color, and text separations (pages 8-9), ca. 1992 (Box OS:, Folder 707)
    - Black and white, color, and text separations (pages 10-11), ca. 1992 (Box OS:, Folder 708)
    - Black and white, color, and text separations (pages 12-13), ca. 1992 (Box OS:, Folder 709)
    - Black and white, color, and text separations (pages 14-15), ca. 1992 (Box OS:, Folder 710)
    - Black and white, color, and text separations (pages 16-17), ca. 1992 (Box OS:, Folder 711)
    - Black and white, color, and text separations (pages 18-19), ca. 1992 (Box OS:, Folder 712)
    - Black and white, color, and text separations (pages 20-21), ca. 1992 (Box OS:, Folder 713)
    - Black and white, color, and text separations (pages 22-23), ca. 1992 (Box OS:, Folder 714)
    - Black and white, color, and text separations (page 24), ca. 1992 (Box OS:, Folder 715)
  - Best Make-It Book Ever, 1977
    - Various black and white separations and drawings, ca. 1977 (Box OS:, Folder 215)
    - Black and white separation (title page), ca. 1977 (Box OS:, Folder 216)
    - Black and white separation with text (pages 2-3), ca. 1977 (Box OS:, Folder 217)
    - Black and white separation with text (pages 4-5), ca. 1977 (Box OS:, Folder 218)
    - Black and white separation with text (pages 6-7), ca. 1977 (Box OS:, Folder 219)
    - Black and white separation with text (pages 8-9), ca. 1977 (Box OS:, Folder 220)
    - Black and white separation with text (pages 10-11), ca. 1977 (Box OS:, Folder 221)
    - Black and white separation with text (pages 12-13), ca. 1977 (Box OS:, Folder 222)
    - Black and white separation (pages 14-15), ca. 1977 (Box OS:, Folder 223)
    - Black and white separation (pages 16-17), ca. 1977 (Box OS:, Folder 224)
    - Black and white separation (pages 18-19), ca. 1977 (Box OS:, Folder 225)
    - Black and white separation with text (pages 22-23), ca. 1977 (Box OS:, Folder 226)
    - Black and white separation with text (pages 24-25), ca. 1977 (Box OS:, Folder 227)
    - Black and white separation with text (pages 26-27), ca. 1977 (Box OS:, Folder 228)
    - Black and white separation with text (pages 30-31), ca. 1977 (Box OS:, Folder 229)
    - Black and white separation with text (pages 32-33), ca. 1977 (Box OS:, Folder 230)
    - Black and white separation with text (pages 34-35), ca. 1977 (Box OS:, Folder 231)
    - Black and white separation with text (pages 36-37), ca. 1977 (Box OS:, Folder 232)
    - Black and white separation with text (pages 38-39), ca. 1977 (Box OS:, Folder 233)
    - Black and white separation with text (pages 40-41), ca. 1977 (Box OS:, Folder 234)
    - Black and white separation with text (pages 42-43), ca. 1977 (Box OS:, Folder 235)
    - Black and white separation with text (pages 44-45), ca. 1977 (Box OS:, Folder 236)
    - Black and white separation with text (pages 46-47), ca. 1977 (Box OS:, Folder 237)
    - Black and white separation with text (pages 48-49), ca. 1977 (Box OS:, Folder 238)
    - Black and white separation with text (pages 48-49), ca. 1977 (Box OS:, Folder 238)
    - Black and white separation with text (pages 50-51), ca. 1977 (Box OS:, Folder 239)
    - Black and white separation with text (pages 52-53), ca. 1977 (Box OS:, Folder 240)
    - Black and white separation with text (pages 54-55), ca. 1977 (Box OS:, Folder 241)
    - Black and white separation with text (pages 56-57), ca. 1977 (Box OS:, Folder 242)
    - Black and white separation with text (pages 58-59), ca. 1977 (Box OS:, Folder 243)
    - Black and white separation with text (pages 60-61), ca. 1977 (Box OS:, Folder 244)
    - Black and white separation with text (pages 62-63), ca. 1977 (Box OS:, Folder 245)
    - Black and white separation with text (pages ), ca. 1977 (Box OS:)
    - Black and white separation (pages 64-65), ca. 1977 (Box OS:, Folder 246)
    - Black and white separation with text (pages 68-69), ca. 1977 (Box OS:, Folder 247)
    - Black and white separation (pages 70-71), ca. 1977 (Box OS:, Folder 248)
    - Black and white separation (pages 72-73), ca. 1977 (Box OS:, Folder 249)
    - Black and white separation (pages 47-75), ca. 1977 (Box OS:, Folder 250)
    - Black and white separation (pages 76-77), ca. 1977 (Box OS:, Folder 251)
    - Black and white separation with text (pages 78-79), ca. 1977 (Box OS:, Folder 252)
    - Black and white separation with text (pages 80-81), ca. 1977 (Box OS:, Folder 253)
    - Black and white separation with text (pages 82-83), ca. 1977 (Box OS:, Folder 254)
    - Black and white separation with text (pages 84-85), ca. 1977 (Box OS:, Folder 255)
    - Black and white separation with text (pages 86-87), ca. 1977 (Box OS:, Folder 256)
    - Black and white separation with text (pages 88-89), ca. 1977 (Box OS:, Folder 257)
    - Black and white separation with text (pages 90-91), ca. 1977 (Box OS:, Folder 258)
    - Black and white separation with text (pages 92-93), ca. 1977 (Box OS:, Folder 259)
    - Black and white separation (pages 94-95), ca. 1977 (Box OS:, Folder 260)
    - Black and white separation with text (pages 96-97), ca. 1977 (Box OS:, Folder 261)
    - Black and white separation with text (pages 98-99), ca. 1977 (Box OS:, Folder 262)
    - Black and white separation with text (pages 100-01), ca. 1977 (Box OS:, Folder 263)
    - Black and white separation with text (pages 102-03), ca. 1977 (Box OS:, Folder 264)
    - Black and white separation with text (pages 104-05), ca. 1977 (Box OS:, Folder 265)
    - Black and white separation with text (pages ), ca. 1977 (Box OS:)
    - Black and white separation with text (pages 108-09), ca. 1977 (Box OS:, Folder 266)
    - Black and white separation with text (pages 110-11), ca. 1977 (Box OS:, Folder 267)
    - Black and white separation with text (pages 114-15), ca. 1977 (Box OS:, Folder 268)
    - Black and white separation with text (pages 116-17), ca. 1977 (Box OS:, Folder 269)
    - Black and white separation with text (pages 118-19), ca. 1977 (Box OS:, Folder 270)
    - Black and white separation with text (pages 118-19), ca. 1977 (Box OS:, Folder 271)
    - Black and white separation with text (pages 120-21), ca. 1977 (Box OS:, Folder 272)
    - Black and white separation with text (pages 122-23), ca. 1977 (Box OS:, Folder 273)
    - Black and white separation with text (pages 124-25), ca. 1977 (Box OS:, Folder 274)
    - Black and white separation with text (pages 126-27), ca. 1977 (Box OS:, Folder 275)
    - Black and white separation with text (pages 128-29), ca. 1977 (Box OS:, Folder 276)
    - Black and white separation with text (pages 130-31), ca. 1977 (Box OS:, Folder 277)
    - Black and white separation with text (pages 132-33), ca. 1977 (Box OS:, Folder 278)
    - Black and white separation with text (pages 134-35), ca. 1977 (Box OS:, Folder 279)
    - Black and white separation with text (pages 136-37), ca. 1977 (Box OS:, Folder 280)
    - Black and white separation (pages 138-39), ca. 1977 (Box OS:, Folder 281)
    - Black and white separation with text (pages 140-41), ca. 1977 (Box OS:, Folder 282)
    - Black and white separation (pages 142-43), ca. 1977 (Box OS:, Folder 283)
    - Color art (cover), ca. 1977 (Box OS:, Folder 284)
    - Color and text separations (cover), ca. 1977 (Box OS:, Folder 285)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 1), ca. 1977 (Box OS:, Folder 286)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 2-3), ca. 1977 (Box OS:, Folder 287)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 4-5), ca. 1977 (Box OS:, Folder 288)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 6-7), ca. 1977 (Box OS:, Folder 289)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 8-9), ca. 1977 (Box OS:, Folder 290)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 10-11), ca. 1977 (Box OS:, Folder 291)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 12-13), ca. 1977 (Box OS:, Folder 292)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 14-15), ca. 1977 (Box OS:, Folder 293)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 16-17), ca. 1977 (Box OS:, Folder 294)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 18-19), ca. 1977 (Box OS:, Folder 295)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 20-21), ca. 1977 (Box OS:, Folder 296)
    - Black and white separations (pages 20-21), ca. 1977 (Box OS:, Folder 297)
    - Black and white, text, and color separations (pages 22-23), ca. 1977 (Box OS:, Folder 298)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 24-25), ca. 1977 (Box OS:, Folder 299)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 26-27), ca. 1977 (Box OS:, Folder 300)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 28-29), ca. 1977 (Box OS:, Folder 301)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 30-31), ca. 1977 (Box OS:, Folder 302)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 32-33), ca. 1977 (Box OS:, Folder 303)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 34-35), ca. 1977 (Box OS:, Folder 304)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 36-37), ca. 1977 (Box OS:, Folder 305)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 38-39), ca. 1977 (Box OS:, Folder 306)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 40-41), ca. 1977 (Box OS:, Folder 307)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 42-43), ca. 1977 (Box OS:, Folder 308)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 44-45), ca. 1977 (Box OS:, Folder 309)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 46-47), ca. 1977 (Box OS:, Folder 310)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 48-49), ca. 1977 (Box OS:, Folder 311)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 50-51), ca. 1977 (Box OS:, Folder 312)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 53 and 55), ca. 1977 (Box OS:, Folder 313)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 56-57), ca. 1977 (Box OS:, Folder 314)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 58-59), ca. 1977 (Box OS:, Folder 315)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 60-61), ca. 1977 (Box OS:, Folder 316)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 62-63), ca. 1977 (Box OS:, Folder 317)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 64-65), ca. 1977 (Box OS:, Folder 318)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 68-69), ca. 1977 (Box OS:, Folder 319)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 70-71), ca. 1977 (Box OS:, Folder 320)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 72-73), ca. 1977 (Box OS:, Folder 321)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 74-75), ca. 1977 (Box OS:, Folder 322)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 76-77), ca. 1977 (Box OS:, Folder 323)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 78-79), ca. 1977 (Box OS:, Folder 324)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 80-81), ca. 1977 (Box OS:, Folder 325)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 82-83), ca. 1977 (Box OS:, Folder 326)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 84-85), ca. 1977 (Box OS:, Folder 327)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 86-87), ca. 1977 (Box OS:, Folder 328)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 88-89), ca. 1977 (Box OS:, Folder 329)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 90-91), ca. 1977 (Box OS:, Folder 330)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 92-93), ca. 1977 (Box OS:, Folder 331)
    - Black and white, color, and text separations (pages 94-95), ca. 1977 (Box OS:, Folder 332)
    - Black and white, color, and text separations (pages 96-97), ca. 1977 (Box OS:, Folder 333)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 98-99), ca. 1977 (Box OS:, Folder 334)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 100-01), ca. 1977 (Box OS:, Folder 335)
    - Black and white, color, and text separations (pages 102-03), ca. 1977 (Box OS:, Folder 336)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 104-05), ca. 1977 (Box OS:, Folder 337)
    - Black and white, color, and text separations (pages 106-07), ca. 1977 (Box OS:, Folder 338)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 108-09), ca. 1977 (Box OS:, Folder 339)
    - Black and white, color, and text separations (pages 110-11), ca. 1977 (Box OS:, Folder 340)
    - Black and white, color, and text separations (pages 112-13), ca. 1977 (Box OS:, Folder 341)
    - Black and white, color, and text separations (pages 114-15), ca. 1977 (Box OS:, Folder 342)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 116-17), ca. 1977 (Box OS:, Folder 343)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 118-19), ca. 1977 (Box OS:, Folder 344)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 120-21), ca. 1977 (Box OS:, Folder 345)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 122-23), ca. 1977 (Box OS:, Folder 346)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 124), ca. 1977 (Box OS:, Folder 347)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 126-27), ca. 1977 (Box OS:, Folder 348)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 129), ca. 1977 (Box OS:, Folder 349)
    - Text separations and blue board (pages 130-31), ca. 1977 (Box OS:, Folder 350)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 130-31), ca. 1977 (Box OS:, Folder 351)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 132-33), ca. 1977 (Box OS:, Folder 352)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 134-35), ca. 1977 (Box OS:, Folder 353)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 136-37), ca. 1977 (Box OS:, Folder 354)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 138-39), ca. 1977 (Box OS:, Folder 355)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 140-41), ca. 1977 (Box OS:, Folder 356)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 143-44), ca. 1977 (Box OS:, Folder 357)
  - Best Mistake Ever, 1984
    - Acetate artwork (24 pieces), ca. 1984 (Box OS:, Folder 358)
    - Black and white and color separations (cover), ca. 1984 (Box OS:, Folder 359)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 1-3), ca. 1984 (Box OS:, Folder 360)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 4-5), ca. 1984 (Box OS:, Folder 361)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 6-7), ca. 1984 (Box OS:, Folder 362)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 8-9), ca. 1984 (Box OS:, Folder 363)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 10-11), ca. 1984 (Box OS:, Folder 364)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 12-13), ca. 1984 (Box OS:, Folder 365)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 14-15), ca. 1984 (Box OS:, Folder 366)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 16-17), ca. 1984 (Box OS:, Folder 367)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 18-19), ca. 1984 (Box OS:, Folder 368)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 20-21), ca. 1984 (Box OS:, Folder 369)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 22-23), ca. 1984 (Box OS:, Folder 370)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 24-25), ca. 1984 (Box OS:, Folder 371)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 26-27), ca. 1984 (Box OS:, Folder 372)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 28-29), ca. 1984 (Box OS:, Folder 373)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 30-31), ca. 1984 (Box OS:, Folder 374)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 32-33), ca. 1984 (Box OS:, Folder 375)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 34-35), ca. 1984 (Box OS:, Folder 376)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 36-37), ca. 1984 (Box OS:, Folder 377)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 38-39), ca. 1984 (Box OS:, Folder 378)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 40-41), ca. 1984 (Box OS:, Folder 379)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 42-43), ca. 1984 (Box OS:, Folder 380)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 44-45), ca. 1984 (Box OS:, Folder 381)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 46-47), ca. 1984 (Box OS:, Folder 382)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 48), ca. 1984 (Box OS:, Folder 383)
  - Best Rainy Day Book Ever, 1974
    - Sketches, ca. 1974 (Box OS:, Folder 397)
    - Color artwork [cover], ca. 1974 (Box OS:, Folder 398)
    - Black and white, color, and text separations (pages 2-3), ca. 1974 (Box OS:, Folder 399)
    - Black and white, color, and text separations (pages 4-5), ca. 1974 (Box OS:, Folder 400)
    - Black and white, color, and text separations (pages 6-7), ca. 1974 (Box OS:, Folder 401)
    - Black and white, color, and text separations (pages 8-9), ca. 1974 (Box OS:, Folder 402)
    - Black and white, color, and text separations (pages10-11), ca. 1974 (Box OS:, Folder 403)
    - Black and white, color, and text separations (pages 12-13), ca. 1974 (Box OS:, Folder 404)
    - Black and white, color, and text separations (pages 14-15), ca. 1974 (Box OS:, Folder 405)
    - Black and white, color, and text separations (pages 16-17), ca. 1974 (Box OS:, Folder 406)
      Some artwork from this spread also used on page 1.
    - Artwork and text (pages 18-19), ca. 1974 (Box OS:, Folder 407)
    - Artwork and text (pages 20-21), ca. 1974 (Box OS:, Folder 408)
    - Artwork and text (pages 22-23), ca. 1974 (Box OS:, Folder 409)
    - Artwork and text (pages 24-25), ca. 1974 (Box OS:, Folder 410)
    - Artwork and text separations (pages 26-27), ca. 1974 (Box OS:, Folder 411)
    - Artwork and text separations (pages 28-29), ca. 1974 (Box OS:, Folder 412)
    - Artwork and text separations (pages 30-31), ca. 1974 (Box OS:, Folder 413)
    - Artwork and text separations (pages 32-33), ca. 1974 (Box OS:, Folder 414)
    - Artwork and text separations (pages 34-35), ca. 1974 (Box OS:, Folder 415)
    - Artwork and text (pages 36-37), ca. 1974 (Box OS:, Folder 416)
    - Artwork and text separations (pages 38-39), ca. 1974 (Box OS:, Folder 417)
    - Artwork and text (pages 40-41), ca. 1974 (Box OS:, Folder 418)
    - Artwork and text (pages 42-43), ca. 1974 (Box OS:, Folder 419)
    - Artwork and text (pages 44-45), ca. 1974 (Box OS:, Folder 420)
    - Artwork and text (pages 46-47), ca. 1974 (Box OS:, Folder 421)
    - Artwork and text (pages 48-29), ca. 1974 (Box OS:, Folder 422)
    - Artwork and text (pages 50-51), ca. 1974 (Box OS:, Folder 423)
    - Artwork and text (pages 52-53), ca. 1974 (Box OS:, Folder 424)
    - Artwork and text (pages 54-55), ca. 1974 (Box OS:, Folder 425)
    - Artwork and text (pages 56-57), ca. 1974 (Box OS:, Folder 426)
    - Artwork and text (pages 58-59), ca. 1974 (Box OS:, Folder 427)
    - Artwork and text (pages 60-61), ca. 1974 (Box OS:, Folder 428)
    - Artwork and text (pages 62-63), ca. 1974 (Box OS:, Folder 429)
    - Artwork and text (pages 64-65), ca. 1974 (Box OS:, Folder 430)
    - Artwork and text (pages 66-67), ca. 1974 (Box OS:, Folder 431)
    - Artwork and text (pages 68-69), ca. 1974 (Box OS:, Folder 432)
    - Artwork and text (pages 70-71), ca. 1974 (Box OS:, Folder 433)
    - Artwork and text (pages 72-73), ca. 1974 (Box OS:, Folder 434)
    - Artwork and text (pages 74-75), ca. 1974 (Box OS:, Folder 435)
    - Artwork and text (pages 76-77), ca. 1974 (Box OS:, Folder 436)
    - Artwork and text (pages 78-79), ca. 1974 (Box OS:, Folder 437)
    - Artwork and text (pages 80-81), ca. 1974 (Box OS:, Folder 438)
    - Artwork and text (pages 82-83), ca. 1974 (Box OS:, Folder 439)
    - Artwork and text (pages 84-85), ca. 1974 (Box OS:, Folder 440)
    - Artwork and text (pages 86-87), ca. 1974 (Box OS:, Folder 441)
    - Artwork and text (pages 88-89), ca. 1974 (Box OS:, Folder 442)
    - Artwork and text (pages 90-91), ca. 1974 (Box OS:, Folder 443)
    - Artwork and text (pages 92-93), ca. 1974 (Box OS:, Folder 444)
    - Artwork and text (pages 94-95), ca. 1974 (Box OS:, Folder 445)
    - Artwork and text (pages 96-97), ca. 1974 (Box OS:, Folder 446)
    - Artwork and text (pages 98-99), ca. 1974 (Box OS:, Folder 447)
    - Artwork and text (pages 100-01), ca. 1974 (Box OS:, Folder 448)
    - Artwork and text (pages 102-03), ca. 1974 (Box OS:, Folder 449)
    - Artwork and text (pages 104-05), ca. 1974 (Box OS:, Folder 450)
    - Artwork and text (pages 106-07), ca. 1974 (Box OS:, Folder 451)
    - Artwork and text (pages 108-09), ca. 1974 (Box OS:, Folder 452)
    - Artwork and text (pages 110-11), ca. 1974 (Box OS:, Folder 453)
    - Artwork and text (pages 112-13), ca. 1974 (Box OS:, Folder 454)
    - Artwork and text (pages 114-15), ca. 1974 (Box OS:, Folder 455)
    - Artwork and text (pages 116-17), ca. 1974 (Box OS:, Folder 456)
    - Artwork and text (pages 118-19), ca. 1974 (Box OS:, Folder 457)
    - Artwork and text (pages 120-21), ca. 1974 (Box OS:, Folder 458)
    - Artwork and text (pages 122-23), ca. 1974 (Box OS:, Folder 459)
    - Artwork and text (pages 124-25), ca. 1974 (Box OS:, Folder 460)
    - Artwork and text (pages 126-27), ca. 1974 (Box OS:, Folder 461)
    - Artwork and text (pages 128-29), ca. 1974 (Box OS:, Folder 462)
    - Artwork and text (pages 130-31), ca. 1974 (Box OS:, Folder 463)
    - Artwork and text (pages 132-33), ca. 1974 (Box OS:, Folder 464)
    - Artwork and text (pages 134-35), ca. 1974 (Box OS:, Folder 465)
    - Artwork and text (pages 136-37), ca. 1974 (Box OS:, Folder 466)
    - Artwork and text (pages 138-39), ca. 1974 (Box OS:, Folder 467)
    - Artwork and text (pages 140-41), ca. 1974 (Box OS:, Folder 468)
    - Artwork and text (pages 142-43), ca. 1974 (Box OS:, Folder 469)
    - Artwork and text (pages 144-45), ca. 1974 (Box OS:, Folder 470)
    - Artwork and text (pages 146-47), ca. 1974 (Box OS:, Folder 471)